Register of the Vladimir Milanović Papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Oversize materials, 1968-1941 (Box 13)
  - Certificates of pilgrimage to the Basilica of the Holy Sepulchre, Jerusalem, 12-25 May 1941; and 23 May-5 June 1941 (Folder 13: 1-2)
  - Royal Yugoslav embassy, Sofia, Bulgaria, 1940 (Folder 13: 3)
    Minutes of the Royal Yugoslav embassy meeting on transferring the office to a new ambassador and inventory lists of the embassy offices in Sofia and Varna